# Azfar Saleem Content Writer

A highly organised and efficient Content Writer whose efforts have yielded significant results from tasks at hand. With nearly 6 years of experience in writing persuasive Content Writing I believe I can become a valuable asset to the company I have applied to.

### **Work Experience**

July 2021-Present

#### Digital Marketing Manager @ IKnowMyToys

Managing an effective team of graphic designers, content writers and social media associates I was able to instruct and guide my team towards increasing sales, engagement of customers with social media updates and the reach of their social updates regarding world-renowned toy brands that they provided to customers in Pakistan. With such responsibilities, I got a wholesome perspective into how effective marketing campaigns are made.

### April 2021 - Technology Content July 2021 Strategist @ VIDIZMO LLC

As a Technology Content Strategist, I am expected to conduct heavy research about current trends of Enterprise Video Content Management Systems and write blogs that increase our websites traffic, while providing prospective customers vital information about the different systems of this market and its current news.

# September 2017 - Digital Marketing April 2021 Manager @ IKnowMyToys

Managing an effective team of graphic designers, content writers and social media associates I was able to instruct and guide my team towards increasing sales, engagement of customers with social media updates and the reach of their social updates regarding world-renowned toy brands that they provided to customers in Pakistan. With such responsibilities, I got a wholesome perspective into how effective marketing campaigns are made.

September 2016-September 2017

## Affiliate Marketing Associate @ Gaditek

Responsible to build strong relationships with gaming influencers who could help promote a product of the company. This product is called "Kill Ping". Excellent writing skills were required for this position, as I was asked to contact such influencers via social media and email often. To persuade them to assist us, which led us to marketing the product effectively.

#### **Personal Data**

Name - Azfar Bilal Saleem Birth - 19th September 1994 City- Karachi, Sindh Mobile - +923352070555 WhatsApp - +923352070555

### Education

August 2013 -June 2016 Kingston University London - BA(Hons.)

Media and Cultural Studies - Upper Second Class